barc.com 2012-06-10

# None

This Privacy Policy describes Barc's policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your information. Barc receives your information through our various services, application(s) and website(s) ( **"Services"** ). For example, you send us information when you register for a Barc account, download Barc software from our web site, post text and other content and otherwise use the Services. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Barc in the United States and anywhere in the world where Barc operates and you use the Services. 

This Privacy Policy is part of the Barc Terms of Service ( **â€œTermsâ€** ) available at Terms of Service, including the Barc Values and Rules, which you agree to upon registration and by your use of the Services. Please read these policies carefully. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@Barc.com](mailto:info@Barc.com). 

##  Collection and Use of Information We Receive From You 

**Information Collected Upon Registration:** When you create or change a Barc account, you provide the following personal information: your username, password, and email address (optional). This information is not public, except your username, which is listed publicly on our Services, including on your HomeScreen, in chats and in search results. 

**Email:** It is your choice whether to provide your email address to us and is entirely optional. We recommend that you do so, as your email address will only be used by us for security or enforcement purposes. We will not use your email address to send you information about our Services or to market to you, nor will we give or sell your e-mail to third parties for marketing purposes. If you email us for any reason, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. 

**HomeScreen Information:** When you use the Services, you create a HomeScreen which contains your username, chat rooms, and names of locations people come to you from. Your Friends List and Private Chats are always private to the users in the Private Chat. However, the other information on your HomeScreen is public unless you choose to limit access to this information by blocking off your HomeScreen from everyone or by blocking individual users in the Barc Options. 

**Your Content:** Our Services allow you to browse the Web and chat with other users browsing the same site(s) and to participate in discussions on any common topic of interest. Much of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to make public and will be accessible to other users of the Services as well as the general public. This includes any chats, text, opinions, reviews and other information, graphics, photos, video or other materials posted, transmitted, uploaded, downloaded or appearing on the Services ( **â€œContentâ€** ). Our default is to make the Content you provide public. The exception to this is your Private Chats, which are always private. Content from your Private Chats is never publicly available and is deleted when the chat is closed. In addition, we give you option of making certain Content and other information unavailable if you want by using certain privacy settings available at Barc Options. 

It is important that you understand that your Content (except in Private Chats) and other public information is broadly and instantly disseminated and may be searchable by everyone, including search engines, except to the extent you have opted to limit access to such information (see Barc Options). If you use the Services to post or otherwise disclose personal information about yourself, except in Private Chats or to the extent you have opted to limit access to such information, all others using the Services and the general public have access to the personal information you provide. Please carefully read the Terms at Terms of Service, including the Barc Values and Rules, regarding ownership, use of and restrictions on Content. 

##  Collection and Use of Your Activity and Usage Information 

Barc, other users and the public have access to information regarding the activity and use of the Services occurring under your username, including the frequency of use, website browsing and preferences and chat room activity and other usage information, except in connection with Private Chats and Friends Lists and when you select certain limited access settings under Barc Options. Barcâ€™s servers do not automatically record information created by your use of the Services, although it may elect to do so from time to time under limited circumstances to ensure that we continue to provide a safe, efficient, and lawful experience. Specifically, we may use this information (i) to provide our services and features to you and to measure and improve those services and features, (ii) to provide you with customer support, (iii) for research, marketing and advertising purposes, (iv) to prevent potentially illegal or harmful activities, and (v) to enforce the Terms. For example, we may log your IP address if your account has been banned, for enforcement of the Terms or as required by law. 

##  Collection and Use of Information We Receive From Third Parties 

We may institute programs with advertising partners and websites in which they share information with us. For example, we may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didnâ€™t see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as â€œconversion tracking,â€ helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see. 

##  Privacy Settings 

The Barc Values and Rules states that our mission includes promoting public discussion and free speech while protecting your privacy. To promote these twin goals, our default is that all Content, HomeScreen and non-personal information, except Friends Lists and Private Chats, is freely accessible by all, although we do provide you the option of limiting access in certain essential ways under the Barc Options. 

##  Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, such as hosting our Services. We may share your information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide these services, under agreements which provide the same protections to your information that we do. 

Law and Harm: We may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the rights or safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; to protect Barc's rights; or property or enforce the Terms. 

Business Transfers: In the event that Barc is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity. 

##  Modifying Your Personal Information 

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account at Manage Account under Barc Options. 

You can also permanently delete your Barc account. If you follow the instructions at Manage Account your account will be deactivated and then deleted. For up to 30 days it is still possible to restore your account if it was accidentally or wrongfully deactivated. After 30 days, we begin the process of deleting your account from our systems, which may not be immediate. All Content you posted prior to deletion of your account (other than that in Private Chats) will remain posted on the Services. 

##  Our Policy Toward Children 

Our Terms require that you must be 18 years or older to use the Services. If you become aware that a child under 18 is using the Services, please delete their account. If we become aware that a child under 18 has opened a Barc account, we will terminate the child's account. 

##  California Residents 

California law permits residents who have provided personal information to us to request information about disclosure of personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes. As detailed above, we do not disclose personal information collected online or otherwise for any third party's direct marketing purposes. However, users may contact us at [info@barc.com](mailto:info@barc.com) if they have any questions regarding this policy. 

##  Security 

We take your security seriously and take reasonable steps to protect your information that you have elected to keep private. However, no data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. We take reasonable, appropriate steps to protect against unauthorized access to, and disclosure of, personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any firewalls or secure server software we may employ. 

Barc adheres to the US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the [U.S. Department of Commerceâ€™s Safe Harbor Program](http://export.gov/safeharbor/). 

##  Changes to this Policy 

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at Privacy Policy. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will notify you via a Barc update. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

Effective: December 3, 2011 

Thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy? Please, let us know at [info@barc.com](mailto:info@barc.com)
